I believe you will find yo creo que te
das cuenta that just with five minute
meditations k comatose in a cinco
minutos you can change your my boys
cambiar tu mente i think if you try to
do 24 subjects in to our meditation SI
creo que intentan hacer en t quattro
Thomasina metas en de dos horas nothing
will change now I cumbia your mind won't
change the momentum no cambia de sao
chai Asik intentalo okay ready listos
you really gonna help you this why are
you that it makes a sound in the
beginning as soon soon your pants EPO
and then you can choose the sound it's
cool when the scope else on your studyin
okay relax your shoulders set up string
relajado home bros derecho relax your
hands full of my nose relax your eyes
relax ojos pull in your stomach a little
bit method to stoneham poquito
smile just a little bit sundry on papito
wei xiao and then slowly started
watching prayer he'll interment in peace
observer to respiration
then I'd like you to think of something
you use every day no study que piensas
en algo cute little Dion you could be
yourself on to sell ruler Poyser your
laptop tu computadora your shoes so
battle think of something new you own
piensa en algo que Gators when you away
Katinas choose one thing is cocaine
those positions
didn't think who made this thing y
piensa que nice west of course it was
made in a factory claro collision fabric
someone invented it allenamento somebody
brought it to the store for you to buy
me no transport toilet in the pocket
polo completas you paid money lo pegaste
con dinero but where did the money come
from but I laundering el dinero where
did the store come from the underwing
all at the end where did the factory
come from in la fábrica on the window
where did the inventor come from here on
the winner inventory go deeper to the
cause of the cost bay parfum de la casa
la causa and the cause of the causes
your own actions y la casa la causa son
tus propios acciones you were very very
generous in the past with the moon week
and rosalyn pasado you gave away
everything mr. Toller and that created
the phone yes of Creole the level and
the laptop la computadora and the shoes
los zapatos and the city that you live
in de la sua on the rivers so think
about Joe SI que pensa and Joe one more
minute Nino Tomas
come back to bed watch Oprah volver a la
respiracion observe ARLA
and then slowly open your eyes I
lentamente oh so close okay